joydesk.com 2001-04-05

# Joydesk.com

|    
Introduction   
  
IP Address   
  
Cookies   
  
Your Account   
  
Other Info.   
  
Personal Info.   
  
Aggregate Info.   
  
Legal Issues   
  
Other Websites' Policies   
  
Security   
  
About Children   
  
Control of your Info.   
  
Your Consent   
  
How to Contact Us   
  
|  | 

|  |  **Privacy Statement for VirtualTek/Joydesk.com** **Introduction** ****

* * *

We know that your privacy is important to you, and we are committed to protecting your privacy. This statement provides our privacy policy for our website: [**_http://joydesk.com_**](http://joydesk.com/) and explains our online information gathering practices and the choices you can make regarding your personal information. Although our privacy policy may change, our commitment to protect your privacy will not.

**Information We Collect**

* * *

VirtualTek collects information online primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, e-mail address, or other contact information. On other occasions such as when you want to purchase our products online, we may request your credit card number to conclude the transaction. Our goal is to provide you with an opportunity to test and purchase our products and services while allowing you to control your privacy. 

  * **IP Address** **  
**

* * *

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When users request a page from our site, our servers log the current IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that while a user session will be tracked, the user will be anonymous. 

  * **Cookies** **  
**

* * *

"Cookies" are pieces of data your browser stores on your computer's hard drive that contain information about your website preferences and website activity. We do not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent the acceptance of cookies. If you elect to reject cookies you can still use our services on our website, but you may be limited in view and functionality. Our policy does not cover the use of cookies by any other companies we choose to have on our site. 

  * **Your Account** **  
**

* * *

When you open an account with VirtualTek, we will ask you for your name, telephone number, industry, zip code, and country. If necessary, we use your contact information for help in processing an order you have placed. We may ask for demographic information and interest-based information when you create an account. However, whether you provide such information is purely optional. 

We may from time to time, use this information to send you alerts about new products, services, or other promotions. We may also ask you to participate in a survey. You can at any time "opt-out" of receiving such communications by sending us an e-mail to the following e-mail address: 

[_info@virtualtek.com_](mailto:info@virtualtek.com). 

  * **Other Information We Collect** **  
**

* * *

When you purchase our products or services, we ask you for information such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, and credit card number. We store and use this information so we can process your order. If necessary, we might use this information to contact you for help in processing the order. 

Whenever you send us comments or feedback in e-mail or letter or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the website, we may collect and store such information. 

**Disclosure of Information**  

  * **Personal Information** **  
**

* * *

Personal information includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, method of payment information, or other data that identifies you as an individual. Your personal information is used by VirtualTek in order to provide you with free trial services or to process your purchase of our products and services. VirtualTek does not sell, trade, rent, or release your personal information to third parties. If we do so in the future, you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" beforehand. 

  * **Aggregate Information** **  
**

* * *

VirtualTek may occasionally share aggregate data about our users, traffic patterns, sales, and other website information with partners, vendors, and reputable third parties. This data, however, does not contain any personally identifying information. For example, we don't disclose that you purchased a specific product, but we may share statistics on how many customers have purchased a specific product. 

  * **Legal Issues** **  
**

* * *

VirtualTek discloses personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 
    * Conform with applicable law or comply with a legal process served on VirtualTek or its website;
    * Protect and defend the rights or property of VirtualTek, the website, or the website's users; or
    * Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

  * **Other Websites' Policies** **  
**

* * *

You might choose to leave our website via links to other websites, including those of our partners. VirtualTek is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content on those websites, nor is it responsible for the cookies those sites might deposit on your hard drive. 

**Security** **  
**

* * *

We incorporate industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of any information you choose to share with us. After your information reaches VirtualTek, it is stored on a secure server, which means it resides behind a firewall and is not readily accessible from outside the company. At that point, your information is only readily accessible by our employees. All such employees sign a confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement, which provides legal confidentiality protections for our users.    
**About Children** **  
**

* * *

For their protection, children are not eligible to use our services. Because we are not a children's website, we do not provide most of the privacy measures that are so important for their protection on the Internet. Thus, we ask that minors do not submit any information to us without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.    
**Control of Your Information** **  
**

* * *

If for some reason you want us to update or remove your personal information from our database, you may send your e-mail request to: [ _info@virtualtek.com_](mailto:info@virtualtek.com) or contact us using one of the methods listed below under How to Contact Us. However, please note that such information may never be completely removed from our database archives because we routinely back up our servers for disaster recovery purposes.    
**Your Consent** **  
**

* * *

By using our website, you are consenting to the collection, storage, and dissemination of data as described above. Any modification to our policy will be posted in this statement so you can readily review our most current policy. VirtualTek also reserves the right to e-mail you regarding changes to our privacy policy or any other matters that may be necessary for the administration of our website.   
**How to Contact Us** **  
**

* * *

We are interested in your comments and feedback regarding our privacy policy. If you have any questions or comments about this policy or our website, please contact: 

_Webmaster or Content Lead  
VirtualTek Corporation  
Ridgewood Corporate Center  
Building E, Suite 201  
170 120th Ave. NE.  
Bellevue, WA 98005  
Website: [_webmaster@virtualtek.com_](mailto:webmaster@virtualtek.com)  
Content: [_content@virtualtek.com_](mailto:content@virtualtek.com)  
_

| Home | Product Tour | Support | Contact | Site Map |  
Copyright © 2000 VirtualTek Corporation. All rights reserved.   
---|---
